苦しくたって
Kurushikutatte
Even though it hurts…
悲しくたって
Kanashikutatte
…even though I feel sad…
コートのなかでは平気なの
Kooto no naka dewa heiki nano
…on the court I feel just fine.
ボールがうなると胸がはずむわ
Booru ga unaru to mune ga hazumu wa
When I hear the ball flying, my heart races.
レシーブ　トス　スパイク
Reshiibu tosu supaiku
Receive. Toss. Spike.
ワン・ツー　ワン・ツー　アタック
Wan tsuu wan tsuu atakku
One-two, one-two! Attack!
だけど涙がでちゃう
Dakedo namida ga dechau
But sometimes I cry.
女の子だもん
Onna no ko damon
I'm a girl, after all.
涙も汗も若いファイトで
Namida mo ase mo wakai faito de
Through the tears and sweat,
putting up a youthful fight…
青空に遠く叫びたい
Aozora ni tooku sakebitai
…under the blue sky, I just want to scream:
アタック　アタック　ナンバーワン
Atakku atakku nanbaa wan
Attack! Attack! Number 1!
アタック　アタック　ナンバーワン
Atakku atakku nanbaa wan
Attack! Attack! Number 1!
—Episode 104—
She's the No. 1